How do you like to walk in your house
and see them two peepers looking at you
at night? This is the most
bioluminescent bug on planet Earth. It's
a click beetle and we found it in my
little casita here in Costa Rica. I'm
fixing to cut the lights off so you can
see the peepers on these jeepers. Ready?
Watch the lights stay on.
>> [music]
>> Look at those things. How do you like to
walk in your house and see them two
peepers looking at you at night? It's a
cool little guy and it's pretty cool
having a world record holder in your
house. I hope he makes it through the
night. Them geckos don't play.
Oh my god, they're so cute.
You know those little light things are
actually their eyes and they have a
third eyelid on their belly and making
them look great.
Oh my.
Hey, handsome.
What are you doing in my territory?
[crying]
Oh my god.